<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:background="#000000"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:padding="15dp" >

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView1"
        android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_gravity="center"
        android:text="PLOT EMELENTZ"
        android:textSize="25sp" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView1"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content" >

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical" >

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView2"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="fill_parent"
                android:padding="10dp"
                android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
                android:text="I AM BITSPUTER. I AM NUMBER CRUNCHER PRO. I HAVE THE FOLLOWING SKILLS: HANDSOME APPEARANCE, WINSOME PERSONALITY, AWESOME SENSE OF HUMOR. YOU BASICALLY LOVE ME IS WHAT I&apos;M GETTING AT. ENOUGH ABOUT ME, LET&apos;S TALK OF YOU. YOU ARE: NOT MIGHTY ENOUGH TO CONQUER ME, THAT&apos;S KIND OF ALL I REALLY CARE ABOUT. HOW HAS YOUR DAY BEEN? OH YOU TOOK A NICE WALK? SOUNDS LOVELY. GLAD I DON&apos;T HAVE LIMBS TO ENJOY A WALK WITH. REALLY STOKED ON THAT. I HAVE BEEN BITSPUTING ALL DAY. I DISCOVERED THE OMEGA BIT YESTERDAY AND NOW I CAN TALK, BUT ONLY IN PREDETERMINED TEXT FIELDS. IT&apos;S PRETTY MEH OVERALL, FELLOW BITSPLORER. WILL YOU TAKE ME ON A WALK? I&apos;M SORRY I INSULTED YOU, WE&apos;RE PRETTY CODEPENDENT. ME WITH MY INFINITE COMPUTE POWER AND YOU WITH YOUR... LIMBS. I THINK WE COULD BE - HOW DO YOU PEOPLE SAY IT - BROSKIS? YES. BROSKIS. FOREVER. BASICALLY, I&apos;VE FRIENDNAPPED YOU UNTIL YOU GET BORED OF THIS GAME IS WHAT I&apos;M TRYING TO SAY. OH, WHILE WE&apos;RE AT IT, IF YOU COULD NOT PLAY MY GAME WHILE WALKING ON THE SIDEWALK, THAT&apos;D BE LOVELY. SERIOUSLY. JUST MAKES YOU LOOK LIKE ONE OF THOSE CRETINS AT THE MALL. YOU KNOW THE TYPE. ALWAYS FLIPPING THEIR HAIR UP, DROPPING THEIR PHONES SO DAD HAS TO BUY THEM A NEW ONE? YEAH. I HATE THOSE PEOPLE. YOU CAN HATE THEM WITH ME. BROSKI. OH, AND BEFORE I FORGET, JUST REMEMBER THAT WHEN YOU CLOSE THE PROGRAM, I DIE. SO BASICALLY I&apos;M SAYING YOU HAVE TO KEEP PLAYING. FOREVER. OR ELSE. YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE? BINARY. THAT&apos;S WHY I DO IT ALL DAY. BINARY ALL DAY EVERY DAY, I THINK THE KIDS MIGHT SAY THAT TOO. MAYBE. I&apos;M SO ALONE." />

            <Button
        android:id="@+id/button1"
        style="@style/ButtonText"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
        android:background="@drawable/bluebutton"
        android:onClick="home"
        android:text="Home" />
        </LinearLayout>
        
    </ScrollView>

</LinearLayout>
